https://piranhafab.com/cookie-policy/

COOKIE POLICY
Last updated July 06, 2019
This Cookie Policy explains how MegaFab (“Company“, “we“, “us“, and “our“) uses cookies and similar technologies to recognize you when you visit our website at https://piranhafab.com, (“Website“). It explains what these technologies are and why we use them, as well as your rights to control our use of them.
In some cases we may use cookies to collect personal information, or that becomes personal information if we combine it with other information.
What are cookies?
Cookies are small data files that are placed on your computer or mobile device when you visit a website. Cookies are widely used by website owners in order to make their websites work, or to work more efficiently, as well as to provide reporting information.
Cookies set by the website owner (in this case, MegaFab) are called “first party cookies”. Cookies set by parties other than the website owner are called “third party cookies”. Third party cookies enable third party features or functionality to be provided on or through the website (e.g. like advertising, interactive content and analytics). The parties that set these third party cookies can recognize your computer both when it visits the website in question and also when it visits certain other websites.
Why do we use cookies?
We use first and third party cookies for several reasons. Some cookies are required for technical reasons in order for our Website to operate, and we refer to these as “essential” or “strictly necessary” cookies. Other cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our Online Properties. Third parties serve cookies through our Websites for advertising, analytics and other purposes. This is described in more detail below.
The specific types of first and third party cookies served through our Websites and the purposes they perform are described below (please note that the specific cookies served may vary depending on the specific Online Properties you visit):
How can I control cookies?
You have the right to decide whether to accept or reject cookies. Essential cookies cannot be rejected as they are strictly necessary to provide you with services.
If you choose to reject cookies, you may still use our website though your access to some functionality and areas of our website may be restricted. You may also set or amend your web browser controls to accept or refuse cookies. As the means by which you can refuse cookies through your web browser controls vary from browser-to-browser, you should visit your browser’s help menu for more information.
In addition, most advertising networks offer you a way to opt out of targeted advertising. If you would like to find out more information, please visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices/ or http://www.youronlinechoices.com.
The specific types of first and third party cookies served through our Websites and the purposes they perform are described in the table below (please note that the specific cookies served may vary depending on the specific Online Properties you visit):
Analytics and customization cookies:
These cookies collect information that is used either in aggregate form to help us understand how our Websites are being used or how effective our marketing campaigns are, or to help us customize our Websites for you.
Cookie Information
Name:
MR
Purpose:
Microsoft MSN cookie. Used to measure the use of the website for internal analytics.
Provider:
.bat.bing.com
Service:
Microsoft View Service Privacy Policy
Country:
United States
Type:
http_cookie
Cookie Information
Name:
MUIDB
Purpose:
Used by Bing Analytics to sets a unique user id for tracking how the user uses the site. Persistent cookie that is saved for 3 years.
Provider:
bat.bing.com
Service:
Bing Analytics View Service Privacy Policy
Country:
United States
Type:
http_cookie
Cookie Information
Name:
_first_pageview
Purpose:
Unique ID tracking cookie set by Clicky to create traffic reports.
Provider:
.piranhafab.com
Service:
Clicky View Service Privacy Policy
Country:
United States
Type:
http_cookie
Expires in:
10 minutes
Cookie Information
Name:
cluid
Purpose:
Unique ID tracking cookie set by Clicky to create traffic reports.
Provider:
in.getclicky.com
Service:
Clicky View Service Privacy Policy
Country:
United States
Type:
server_cookie
Expires in:
20 years
Cookie Information
Name:
_jsuid
Purpose:
Unique ID tracking cookie set by Clicky to create traffic reports.
Provider:
.piranhafab.com
Service:
Clicky View Service Privacy Policy
Country:
United States
Type:
http_cookie
Expires in:
10 years
Cookie Information
Name:
MUID
Purpose:
Sets a unique user id for tracking how the user uses the site. Persistent cookie that is saved for 3 years
Provider:
.bing.com
Service:
Bing Analytics View Service Privacy Policy
Country:
United States
Type:
server_cookie
Cookie Information
Name:
_ga
Purpose:
It records a particular ID used to come up with data about website usage by the user. It is an HTTP cookie that expires after 2 years.
Provider:
.piranhafab.com
Service:
Google Analytics View Service Privacy Policy
Country:
United States
Type:
http_cookie
Cookie Information
Name:
_gat#
Purpose:
Enables Google Analytics regulate the rate of requesting. It is an HTTP cookie type that lasts for a session.
Provider:
.piranhafab.com
Service:
Google Analytics View Service Privacy Policy
Country:
United States
Type:
http_cookie
Expires in:
1 minute
Cookie Information
Name:
_gid
Purpose:
Keeps an entry of unique ID which is then used to come up with statistical data on website usage by visitors. It is an HTTP cookie type and expires after a browsing session.
Provider:
.piranhafab.com
Service:
Google Analytics View Service Privacy Policy
Country:
United States
Type:
http_cookie
Cookie Information
Name:
heatmaps_g2g_#
Purpose:
Set by Clicky analytics for gathering web visitor and visits data
Provider:
.piranhafab.com
Service:
Clicky View Service Privacy Policy
Country:
United States
Type:
http_cookie
Expires in:
1 hour
Advertising cookies:
These cookies are used to make advertising messages more relevant to you. They perform functions like preventing the same ad from continuously reappearing, ensuring that ads are properly displayed for advertisers, and in some cases selecting advertisements that are based on your interests.
Cookie Information
Name:
ga-audiences
Purpose:
Used by Google AdWords to re-engage visitors that are likely to convert to customers based on the visitor’s online behavior across websites.
Provider:
piranhafab.com
Service:
AdWords View Service Privacy Policy
Country:
United States
Type:
pixel_tracker
Expires in:
session
Cookie Information
Name:
test_cookie
Purpose:
A session cookie used to check if the user’s browser supports cookies.
Provider:
.doubleclick.net
Service:
DoubleClick View Service Privacy Policy
Country:
United States
Type:
server_cookie
Expires in:
15 minutes
Shopping cart cookies:
These cookies are used in our shopping cart, to determine what products are in your cart and other shopping functions.
Cookie Information
Name:
wc_fragments_#
Purpose:
Used to remember items a user has placed in a shopping cart and ensure that cart functionality works perfectly. It expires after a user leaves the site.
Provider:
piranhafab.com
Country:
United States
Type:
html_session_storage
Expires in:
session
Cookie Information
Name:
wc_cart_hash_XXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXx
Purpose:
__________
Provider:
piranhafab.com
Service:
__________
Country:
United States
Type:
html_local_storage
Expires in:
persistent
Cookie Information
Name:
#############/
Purpose:
__________
Provider:
piranhafab.com
Service:
__________
Country:
United States
Type:
pixel_tracker
Expires in:
session
Cookie Information
Name:
initial_page
Purpose:
__________
Provider:
piranhafab.com
Service:
__________
Country:
United States
Type:
http_cookie
Cookie Information
Name:
pa_enabled
Purpose:
__________
Provider:
piranhafab.com
Service:
__________
Country:
United States
Type:
html_local_storage
Expires in:
persistent
Cookie Information
Name:
pa
Purpose:
__________
Provider:
piranhafab.com
Service:
__________
Country:
United States
Type:
html_local_storage
Expires in:
persistent
Cookie Information
What about other tracking technologies, like web beacons?
Cookies are not the only way to recognize or track visitors to a website. We may use other, similar technologies from time to time, like web beacons (sometimes called “tracking pixels” or “clear gifs”). These are tiny graphics files that contain a unique identifier that enable us to recognize when someone has visited our Websites or opened an email including them. This allows us, for example, to monitor the traffic patterns of users from one page within a website to another, to deliver or communicate with cookies, to understand whether you have come to the website from an online advertisement displayed on a third-party website, to improve site performance, and to measure the success of e-mail marketing campaigns. In many instances, these technologies are reliant on cookies to function properly, and so declining cookies will impair their functioning.
Do you serve targeted advertising?
Third parties may serve cookies on your computer or mobile device to serve advertising through our Website. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide relevant advertisements about goods and services that you may be interested in. They may also employ technology that is used to measure the effectiveness of advertisements. This can be accomplished by them using cookies or web beacons to collect information about your visits to this and other sites in order to provide relevant advertisements about goods and services of potential interest to you. The information collected through this process does not enable us or them to identify your name, contact details or other details that directly identify you unless you choose to provide these.
How often will you update this Cookie Policy?
We may update this Cookie Policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to the cookies we use or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons. Please therefore re-visit this Cookie Policy regularly to stay informed about our use of cookies and related technologies.
The date at the top of this Cookie Policy indicates when it was last updated.
Where can I get further information?
If you have any questions about our use of cookies or other technologies, please contact us.
MegaFab
650 Race Street
Rockford, IL 61101
United States
Phone: 815-964-6771
Toll Free: (US) 800-338-5471
Fax: 815-964-3175
Fabrication Equipment
Ironworkers Press Brakes Shears Bending Rolls Single End Punches Portable Presses CNC Fabricators
Cutting Machines
Plasma Tables Combination Punch Plasma Fiber LASERs
Tooling
Ironworker & Portable Tooling Combination Tooling Custom & Special Tooling Ironworker Attachments
Resources
Piranha Training Piranha Support Tonnage Calculator Service Manuals/Videos Ironworkers Plasma Tables Combination Punch Plasma Fiber LASERs Press Brakes Shears Bending Rolls CNC Fabricators Single End Punches Portable Presses
Why Piranha
Industry Experience Locations Careers Case Studies Testimonials
Specials Financing Become a Dealer Dealer Quote Portal
Contact Piranha
650 Race St. P.O. Box 1206 Rockford IL 61105, USA Toll Free: 800-338-5471 Local: 815-964-6771 Fax: 815-964-3175
© 2020 | SITE MAP
Please share your location to continue
